<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MorbidMeter Lite</string>
    <string name="help_message">MorbidMeter Lite is a free version of MorbidMeter.
        The Lite version has more limited timescales and update frequencies than
        the full paid version.  In addition, there are no notifications, reverse time, or 
        millisecond intervals in the Lite version.  If you like the Lite version, the
        paid version is only 99 cents.
        \n\nMorbidMeter tracks your lifespan over an alternative timescale.
        For example, using a single year as a timescale and an estimated longevity of 80 years,
        a person in their 40s would have a MorbidMeter date sometime in the summer. 
        Using a day-long
        timescale, the MorbidMeter time would be around noon.
        \n\nUse the configuration screen shown when you start the
        widget or touch the Skull button to set the timescale as well as other widget
        parameters.  Fill in your name, birth date, and
        predicted longevity in years. You will need to pick a longevity.
        There are sites on the Internet that can predict your longevity.
        \n\nTimescales ending in S such as DAYS give the total number of days (or other
        time period)
        you have been alive, whereas the DAY timescale stretches your life over a single day.
        PERCENT gives the percentage of your life you have lived, and UNIVERSE 
        stretches your life to the life of the universe, estimated at 15 billion years (or use
        the X-UNIVERSE options if you believe the earth is 6000 years old). You can reverse time
        and/or add milliseconds in some of the timescales.  Select Show Notifications and pick
        a notification sound if you want to be notified when you reach a MorbidMeter milestone
        (e.g. an hour of MorbidMeter time has passed).  
        \n\nYou can have multiple different MorbidMeter widgets
        on your screen with different parameters at the same time.  
        Long press and drag to the trash any MorbidMeter widget
        that you are done with. Change the update frequency, but use a longer frequency
        if it seems that the widget is draining the battery or you don\'t need
        a fast updates.</string>

</resources>